BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Painters, 1937-1942 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Painters, 1939-1942 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1932-1937 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1932-1939 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1937-1940 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1936-1938 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), local 30, 1938-1939 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Operative Plasterers, 1936-1939 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1936-1939 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1936-1940 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1937-1942 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1936-1941 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1937-1941 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1936-1941 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1939-1941 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1936-1942 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1937-1942 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Operative Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association (O.P. & C.F.I.A.), 1937-1943 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Journeymen Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1934-1940 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Plumber and Steamfitter unions, 1936-1937 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1935-1938 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1937-1939 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1937-1939 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1938-1940 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1936-1941 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1937-1940 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1937-1942 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1936-1942 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1936-1942 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Some agreements marked as confidential.
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1937-1941 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1936-1941 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1938-1941 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1937-1942 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1940-1942 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, 1940-1942 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Roofers, 1937-1939 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Roofers, 1937-1939 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Roofers, 1937-1939 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Roofers, 1936-1938 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Roofers, 1936-1938 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Roofers, 1937-1938 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Roofers, 1938-1939 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Roofers, 1936-1937 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Roofers, 1938 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Roofers, 1938-1939 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Roofers, Indiana, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Roofers, 1940 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Roofers, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Roofers, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Roofers, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Roofers, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Roofers, New York, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Roofers, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Roofers, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Roofers, Washington, DC, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Roofers, 1933-1941 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Roofers, Ohio, 1939-1941 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Roofers, Washington, DC, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Roofers, 1939-1941 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Roofers, 1940-1942 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Roofers, Arizona, 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Roofers, 1940-1942 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Roofers, 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - Roofers, Wisconsin, 1942-1943 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Roofers, 1940-1942 (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Roofers, 1940-1942 (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - Roofers, AFL, California, 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - Hod-Carriers, Building, and Common Laborers, 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Stove Mounters, 1940-1941 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Roofers, 1940-1941 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Stove Mounters, 1936-1938 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Stove Mounters, 1937 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Stove Mounters, 1937-1938 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Stove Mounters, 1937-1938 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Stove Mounters, 1937-1939 (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Stove Mounters, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - Furniture Workers, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, Construction and General Contracting, 1938-1940 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Construction and General Contracting, 1937-1942 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1941, Construction and General Contracting (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Carpenters, AFL, 1939-1943 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, AFL, 1938-1942 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, AFL, 1942-1945 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Hodcarriers, Building, and Common Laborers, AFL, 1941-1945 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Construction Workers, CIO, 1941-1945 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Painters, Decorators, and Paper-hangers, AFL, 1942-1944 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, AFL, 1942-1944 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Construction, 1937-1941 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Shell Pipe Line Corporation - Bayon Pipe Line System, 1943 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Construction Companies, 1943-1944 (Box 129, Folder 25)
- Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing (Food, Animal Food, Butchering, Bakeries, Beverage and Tobacco, Textile, Apparel, Leather, Footwear)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (AZ, AR, and CA), 1914-1937 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Documents in English and Yiddish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (CO, CT, and DC), 1922-1937 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (GA, ID, and IL), 1922-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (Chicago, IL), 1909-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    agreements in English, Yiddish, German, Slovak, and Polish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (IN, IA, KS, KY, and LA), 1922-1937 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (MD, MA, and MI), 1922-1936 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    agreements in English, Yiddish, and Polish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (MN and MO), 1912-1937 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Agreements in English and Yiddish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (MT, NV, NH, and NJ), 1921-1937 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Agreements in English and Polish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (NYC), 1921-1937 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Agreements in English, Italian, Yiddish, and Czech
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (NY), 1925-1937 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (OH), 1927-1937 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers and others (OK, OR, PA, and RI), 1921-1937 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers (TN, TX, WA, WV, and WI), 1922-1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Boot and Shoe Workers, 1923-1937 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (CA, CO, and FL), 1925-1937 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (IL and IN), 1927-1937 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (IA, KY, and LA), 1911-1937 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Agreements in English and German.
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (MD, MA, and MI), 1912-1937 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (MN, MO, and MT), 1904-1937 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (NE, NV, NH, and NJ), 1912-1937 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (NY), 1905-1937 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (OH, OK, and PA), 1920-1940 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (RI, TN, TX, VA, and WA), 1904-1937 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers (WV, WI, and WY), 1911-1937 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Agreements in English and German
  - Tobacco Workers and Cigar Makers, 1901-1937 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, Canada, 1929-1932 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Contains only reports from arbitrator
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, Illinois, 1919-1937 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, New York, 1920-1942 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers (MD, MA, MN, and NJ), 1928-1937 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers (OH, PA, VA, and WI), 1922-1941 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers (CA and CO), 1934-1937 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, breweries (CA, CO, DC, IL, and IN), 1908-1937 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, breweries (LA, MD, MA, and MI), 1903-1933 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, breweries (MN), 1902-1936 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, breweries (MO, MT, NJ, NY, OH, and WA), 1904-1924 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Federal Local Unions, food and textile manufacturing, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (AR, CA, and DC), 1913-1926 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (IL and IA), 1914-1923 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (LA and MA), 1912-1928 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (MO, NE, and NJ), 1912-1926 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (NY), 1912-1936 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (OK and VA), 1923 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (general) (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Firemen and Oilers, AFL (MI and MN), 1914-1927 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fur Workers, 1919-1935 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (NY), 1922-19336 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (CA, CT, GA, IL, MA, MN, and MO), 1929-1936 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (OH, OR, WA, and WI), 1919-1936 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - United Garment Workers, AFL, 1919-1936 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hosiery Workers, 1930-1938 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Hosiery Workers, decisions of impartial chairman, 1929-1932 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers, Wisconsin, 1913-1921 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers, general, 1903-1923 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - National Leather Workers, 1933-1937 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - United Leather Workers, AFL, 1926-1937 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Machinists (bakeries, breweries, dairies), 1932-1936 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Amalgamated Meatcutters (AL, CA, DC, and IL), 1925-1937 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Amalgamated Meatcutters (IN, IA, KS, MA, MI, MN, and MT), 1921-1936 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Amalgamated Meatcutters (NY, OH, and OR), 1927-1936 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Amalgamated Meatcutters (PA, TX, UT, WA, and WI), 1926-1937 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Pocketbook Workers, IL and NY, 1921-1935 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Pocketbook, general, 1924-1935 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - United Shoe Workers, 1934-1936 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Shoe Workers Protective Union, 1923-1935 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Journeymen Tailors, AFL (CA, CT, DC, GA, and IL), 1901-1936 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Journeymen Tailors, AFL (IN, IA, KS, MI, MO, MT, NE, NJ, and NY), 1900-1937 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Journeymen Tailors, AFL (OH, OR, PA, RI, TN, TX, VA, WI, and Canada), 1900-1936 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Teamsters, AFL (TN, TX, UT, and VA), 1934-1937 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Teamsters, AFL (WA, WV, and WI), 1919-1938 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - United Textile Workers, AFL, general (CA, CT, GA, and IL), 1924-1937 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - United Textile Workers, AFL, (ME, MA, NJ, NY, and OH), 1889-1937 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - United Textile Workers, AFL, and Textile Workers Organizing Committee, CIO (PA, SC, WI), 1933-1937 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Amalgamated Food Workers, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Glove Workers, 1916-1929 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Documents - Textiles, 1889-1937 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Documents from England, Scotland, and India
  - Needle Trades Workers, 1932-1934 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Suitcase, Bag, and Portfolio Makers, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Documents in English, Polish, and Czech
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1935-1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Documents in English, Yiddish, and Czech
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1935-1939 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1936-1939 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Documents in English, Polish, and Yiddish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1935-1939 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Documents in English, Yiddish, and Polish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1935-1939 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1936-1941 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Some documents marked as confidential; documents in English and Yiddish
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL and United Bakery Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL and United Bakery and Biscuit Workers, CIO, 1937-1941 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Some documents marked as confidential
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1939-1941 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1941 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1941 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Documents in English, Czech, and Yiddish; some documents marked as confidential
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL and United Bakery Workers, CIO, 1938-1941 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1941 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1937-1941 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1941 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL and Retail and Wholesale Employees, CIO, 1937-1941 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1938-1941 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1937-1942 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1939-1942 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL and United Bakery Workers, CIO, 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1943 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1940-1944 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1944 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1944 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1944 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1945 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1945 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1945 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1945 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1945 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1945 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1943-1945 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, AFL, 1942-1945 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1939 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1933-1939 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1937-1939 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1936-1940 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1934-1939 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1939 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1939 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1934-1939 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1933-1940 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1939 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1939 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1938-1940 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1940 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1936-1940 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1940 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1940 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1934-1940 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1936-1940 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1937-1940 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1938-1940 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1936-1940 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1937-1941 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1939-1941 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1938-1941 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1936-1941 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1934-1941 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1937-1941 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1936-1942 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1937-1941 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1935-1941 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1939-1941 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1939-1941 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1940-1943 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1940-1943 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1940-1944 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1942-1944 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1943-1946 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1941-1945 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers, 1942-1945 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Cigarmakers, 1918-1938 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Cigarmakers, 1920-1939 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Cigarmakers, 1921-1939 (Box 38, Folder 15)